Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Physics, Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Physics, honors theses
1978-2009
SC4-4471
Stanford University. Department of Physics.
6.5 Linear feet (197 volumes in 13 boxes)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Department of Physics.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives by the Department of Physics in 1997, by the Physics Library in 2010-2011, and by the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Scope and Contents note
This collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Department of Physics.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Department of Physics.; Stanford University. Libraries. Physics Library.; Physics--Study and teaching.; Student papers.
Collection Contents
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1997-092
  - Aiello, W. A., Flight dynamics of ring airfoil toys., 1983 (Box 1)
  - Babbitt, William Randall, The effects of additional harmoics, FM, and Am in the RF cavity of an electron storage ring., June 1982 (Box 1)
  - Bolton, Tim, The physics of radiological warfare., June 1982 (Box 1)
  - Brock, Joel D., Tight-binding theory in ionic crystals., March 1981 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Stephen James, Experiments with a simplified energy balance mode of the earth's climate., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Cheu, Elliott, A prototype vertex chamber for the Mark III Experiment., May 1986 (Box 1)
  - Cornell, Eric, Ultra low pressure vapor pressure measurements on surface-adsorbed helium-4., June 1985 (Box 1)
  - Cribbs, Randolph K., Fluorescence lifetime measurements of rare earth metals used in fluoroimmunoassay techniques., June 1986 (Box 1)
  - Dale, Daniel S., Picosecond laser excitation in crystalline silicon., 1984 (Box 1)
  - Dandliker, Richard B., An investigation of carbide formation in diamond thin films using transmission electron microscopy., May 1992 (Box 1)
  - Dempsey, Jed, A method for visual pattern recognition in a self-organizing system., September 1981 (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Henry L., Background due to cosmic protons in gamma-ray telescopes., June 1990 (Box 1)
  - Ehrichs, Edward E., A thin film circuit for gravitational wave detection., June 1986 (Box 1)
  - Eisgruber, Ingrid, Hall effect characterization of semiconductor thin films., 1989 (Box 1)
  - Evans, Scott, Time evolution of solar magnetic fluxtube strength., June 1990 (Box 2)
  - Feffer, Paul T., Site selective doping and high temperature superconductivity in (La1-7Pry)(Ba2-xLax)Cu3O7)., 1988 (Box 2)
  - Freeman, William T., Light-paths through oblate planet atmospheres; calculations for Voyager., June 1979 (Box 1)
  - Frieman, Josh, Lost horizon: galazy formation in an inflationary universe., May 1981 (Box 2)
  - Ganz, Eric, Two dimensional spin systems., Spring 1982 (Box 2)
  - Gibson, Sarah, Supergranule power leakage into modes of solar oscillation., 1989 (Box 2)
  - Gooding, Andrew K., A test levitator for niobium spheres., August 1986 (Box 2)
  - Green, James C., Venus and tectonics., March 1982 (Box 2)
  - Haakenaasen, Randi, Construction of a scanning tunneling microscope., 1988 (Box 2)
  - Hamilton, Douglas P., Theoretical optical and UV line intensities from intracluster plasmas., May 1988 (Box 2)
  - House, Michael, Physical and Medical Problems of Laser Angioplasty., June 1986 (Box 2)
  - Hwa, Terence Tai-Li, Proposals to determine the electroweak contribution to Muon's g-2 anamoly., 1986 (Box 2)
  - Jacobs, Polly, Power loss measurements on proton-exchanged LiNb03 waveguides using the Fabry Perot technique., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - Jernigan, Tamara Elizabeth, Transmission of black body radiation through sapphire fibers for remote temperature measurements., June 1981 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Nam Hoon, Study of frequency dependence of eddy-current loss and signal-to-noise ration in MRI., September 1985 (Box 3)
  - King, Richard Roland, Hot prospects in solar cavity receivers., May 1985 (Box 3)
  - Kirk, Randolph, Enhancement algorithms for coronary angiography by means of digital synchrotron dichromography., June 1981 (Box 3)
  - Koh Towsian, Danny, Quasi-elastic electron scattering at high momentum transfer in nuclei and nucleons., June 1990 (Box 3)
  - LaBelle, James, Investigations of the trimpi effect: whistler-induced perturbation of signals propagating in the earth-ionosphere waveguide., June 1980 (Box 3)
  - Labrador, Allan W., Temperature dependence of the contact potential of copper., June 1989 (Box 3)
  - Langenbrunner, James, Crystal counters KRS-5 T1Br T1C1., 1983 (Box 3)
  - Larson, Melora, A thermal model of the gimballed gyroscope test facility., June 1986 (Box 3)
  - Lawall, John R., Laser spectroscopy using radio-frequency optogalvanic detection in neon, helium and sodium., 1983 (Box 3)
  - Lederman, David, Diffusive thermal conductivity in superfluid helum., 1988 (Box 3)
  - Lesko, Kevin Thomas, The development of a recoil doppler apparatus to measure lifetimes and magnetic moments of short lived nuclear states., June 1978 (Box 3)
  - Lim, Eric J., Optical absorption in sapphire., June 1986 (Box 3)
  - Luu, Jane, Anomalous thermal noise in SQUID magnetometers, or (Jane meets the SQUID)., March 1984 (Box 3)
  - Marcus, Charles, The effect of low frequency ambient magnetic fields on the control unit and RF head of a commercial SQUID magnetometer., 1984 (Box 4)
  - Markwardt, Craig, Simulation of light collection by thin scintillator., June 1992 (Box 4)
  - Marshall, Jill Ann, Silicon-on-sapphire 4-point thermometer., 1980 (Box 4)
  - McEachern, Randall L., The search on niobium fragments for fractionally charged particles produced in heavy ion collisions., June 1983 (Box 4)
  - Moler, Kathryn A., Construction of a scanning tunneling microscope., 1988 (Box 4)
  - Navarro, Jose, Deviations of matter from charge neutrality., June 1988 (Box 4)
  - Nelson, Ann, A bizarre star: or, a detailed study of models for the Weird Object SS433., June 1980 (Box 4)
  - Noack, Reinhard M., A normal modes solution for a string with an absorbing boundary., May 1985 (Box 5)
  - Omohundro, Stephen, Some topological excitations in physics., May 1980 (Box 5)
  - Orth, Karen, A passive solar water still., May 1990 (Box 5)
  - Patience, Jennifer L., Modeling coronal bright points as small X-ray emitting loops., 1992 (Box 5)
  - Phillips, Thomas J., Measuring the energy dependence of the time constant for buildup of polarization at SPEAR., 1979 (Box 5)
  - Quake, Stephen, The elastic spring properties of DNA., 1991 (Box 5)
  - Rahn, Jeffrey T., Statistical evidence for pulsar alignment., August 1991 (Box 5)
  - Read, Kenneth F., PSI' ---> PI+ PI- PSI Charmonium decay in SLAC's crystal ball., June 1981 (Box 5)
  - Regan, Brian Christopher, Lightning-induced perturbations of the earth-ionosphere waveguide., June 1992 (Box 5)
  - Roy, Mousumi, SLC moller polarimeter target foil polarization measurements., 1989 (Box 5)
  - Sakazaki, Lloyd Eugene, Solitons and the Fermi-Pasta-Ulam problem., June 1980 (Box 5)
  - Seiffert, Mike, Investigations of ballistic phonon propagation., June 1986 (Box 5)
  - Sethuraman, Srinivasan, Determination of flame temperature using degenerate four-wave mixing., June 1992 (Box 5)
  - Shevitz, Danny, Cosmological constraints on massive neutrinos., June 1985 (Box 6)
  - Shrauner, Jay Arthur, Solar cycle variation in photospheric magnetic field inclination., June 1991 (Box 6)
  - Sobon, Wayne, Coincidence detection of gravitational radiation: a collaboration between the University of Maryland and Stanford University., May 1985 (Box 6)
  - Swift, Peter, The oscillation of a scalar field-dominated universe., June 1990 (Box 6)
  - Sze, Hsuan, Magnetic penetration depth measurements in superconducting thin films., June 1989 (Box 6)
  - Terman, Martin, Determination of the collision center of mass energy of the SLC., 1989 (Box 6)
  - Thomas, Jim, Low energy gamma ray spectroscopy at the J/?., June 1982 (Box 6)
  - Thompson, Peter Alan, A parallel plate avalanche detector for heavily ionizing recoils in gaseous 4heat 1 ATM and 5-degree K., December 1984 (Box 6)
  - Wai, Lawrence Lee, The effect of trapped magnetic flux quanta on the London readout in GP-B., June 1989 (Box 6)
  - Wales, Carolyn, Time resolved measurements of electron energy spectra at the SCA/FEL., March 1990 (Box 6)
  - Widrow, Lawrence Marc, Hydromagnetic phenomena in the sun and stars., May 1984 (Box 6)
  - Wooding, Michael A., Computer simulation of helium gas spinup of cryogenic gyroscope for the relativity gyroscope experiment and a planned experimental parametric test., 1986 (Box 6)
  - Yeh, Sabrina and Robert Liu, Building a high-q, low frequency torsional oscillator (or How we became the gravity twins)., 1991 (Box 6)
  - Zingmond, David Scott, Picosecond pulse compression and amplification., September 1986 (Box 6)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2010-075
  - Abrams, Daniel S., Random motion, quantum chaos, and Ohm's law., June 1994 (Box 1)
  - Adam, Shaffique, Acoustic detection of the highest energy cosmic rays., March 2000 (Box 1)
  - Balick, Daniel, Inflation from a sequestered brane scenario., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Barkats, Denis, Luminosity profiles of spiral and elliptical galaxies., June 1998 (Box 1)
  - Beem, Christopher J., Controlling lambda in IIB flux compactifications., June 2006 (Box 1)
  - Bhatnagar, Aparna, Thin film measurement for AFM in liquids., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Bien, Jacob, Protein motions and mutation from a molecular dynamics viewpoint., June 2006 (Box 1)
  - Birnbaum, Kevin Michael, Open quantum dot in a parallel magnetic field., June 1999 (Box 1)
  - Bleszynski, Ania, Polymers and near shear flows., June 2000 (Box 1)
  - Bokenkamp, Nathaniel, Statistical relationships between solar active region photospheric magnetic properties and flare events., June 2007 (Box 1)
  - Bozovic, Dolores, Optical labeling using plasmon-resonant silver spheres., June 1995 (Box 1)
  - Brizius, Alison R., Modeling and characterization of feedhorns for the Sunyaev Zel'dovich infrared experiment. [2 copies], June 2004 (Box 1)
  - Brooks, Peter, Pulse fitting and energy resolution in the cryogenic dark matter search experiment., June 2007 (Box 1)
  - Chan, Ian Hun Yun, Ballistic conductance fluctuations in shape space. (Box 1)
  - Chong, Y.D., Metallic nature of the four-dimensional quantum hall edge., June 2003 (Box 1)
  - Coleman, Stuart, Ultra-low background alpha counting and analysis., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Connolly, Colin, Resolution enhancement in capacitance pressure gauges for use in melting curve thermometry. [2 copies], June 2004 (Box 1)
  - Datta-Barua, Seebany, Test-bed design for measurement of bolometer optical efficiency at millimeter wavelengths. (Box 1)
  - Deaconu, Cosmin, Analysis of the effect of precise vertexing on tall polarization measurements in the SiD., June 2009 (Box 1)
  - Donaghy, Timothy Q., The stochastic acceleration of plasma particles in solar flares., June 1999 (Box 1)
  - East, William, Heating and acceleration of electrons in the intracluster medium of clusters of galaxies., June 2008 (Box 1)
  - Eclov, Neville, Testing the "blazar sequence" with CGRaBS blazars., June 2009 (Box 1)
  - Fang-Yen, Chris, Fluctuational electric field and many-electron magnetotransport in a nondegenerate 2D electron system., June 1995 (Box 1)
  - Fei, Edward, Data analysis for GP-B gyroscope charge measurement., June 2007 (Box 1)
  - Goel, Anita, The use of the optical tweezers tool to visualize real time transcription by single molecules of RNA polymerase. (Box 1)
  - Grefenstette, Brian, Overview of a TES instrument and data acquisition system., June 2004 (Box 2)
  - Hall, Christina, Creating and testing a dynamic model of human thermoregulation., June 2008 (Box 2)
  - Hart, Sean, Quasiparticle transport and phase separation in transition edge sensors., June 2009 (Box 2)
  - Hartman, Joel, Correction of nanoflare statistics for truncation bias. (Box 2)
  - Hegyi, Alex, Tuning of optical microdisk resonant wavelength by nitrogen condensation., June 2008 (Box 1)
  - Hoedl, Seth A., The luminosity functions of three Abell clusters., 1998 (Box 2)
  - Holme, Timothy P., On the magnetic and transport properties of single-crystal R6Mo4Al43 (R=Y, Gd-Ho, Lu)., May 2003 (Box 2)
  - House, Michael, Physical and medical problems of laser angioplasty., June 1986 (Box 2)
  - Hsieh, David, Making a Bose-Einstein condensate of dilute rubium-87 gas., June 2003 (Box 2)
  - Hunt, Tom, Atomic force microscope lithography., May 2001 (Box 2)
  - Husen, Annalise Noelle, The current levels and conductance of the voltage-gated K channel G87R from squid stellate ganglion. [2 copies], June 1999 (Box 2)
  - Irvin, Casey, Carbon nanotube to the tip of an etched Tungsten tip for electron field emission research under DC voltage., June 2007 (Box 2)
  - Kaplan, Jared, Anthropic fine tuning via vacuum stability., May 2005 (Box 2)
  - Kasen, Daniel, The rotation of spiral galaxies., June 1997 (Box 2)
  - Kato, Saul, Schrodinger waves, antiferromagnetism, and "electron" decay., June 1995 (Box 2)
  - Keeler, Cynthia, Approximation methods for exclusive Higgs Boson production processes in proton and heavy ion collisions., May 2003 (Box 2)
  - Kirby, Evan, Complete characterization of one pixel of the quad prototype. [2 copies], May 2004 (Box 2)
  - Kozaczuk, Jonathan A., Precise determination of the spin speed and spin down rate of gravity probe B gyroscopes., May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Kumar, Ashok, Micro-magnetic tweezers: the development and characterization of a useful probe for the biophysicist's toolbox., May 2007 (Box 2)
  - Landhuis, David P., Picosecond infrared photon echoes and the study of vibrational dynamics in a molecular crystal., June 1994 (Box 2)
  - Leistra, Andrea, Large-scale structure at z~2., June 1998 (Box 3)
  - Leyton, Michael, The silicon tracker of the gamma ray large area space telescope., May 2003 (Box 3)
  - Libby, Elizabeth, Characterization of grating substrates for LISA., May 2005 (Box 3)
  - Ligon, Aaron, A microwire grid for the manipulation of superparamagnetic beads., June 2006 (Box 3)
  - Livnat, Noam and Michael Okun, Observation of the Sagnac effect in a nonplanar ring oscillator., June 1998 (Box 3)
  - Lo, Dennis, Search for the Sgoldstino Boson in E+E- collisions., June 2008 (Box 3)
  - Luna, Katherine, Modeling superconducting microwave oscillators to test for Lorentz violations., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Mainzer, Amanda K., A definitive signature of black holes., June 1995 (Box 3)
  - Maloney, Alexander, The evolution and luminosity function of quasars from complete optical surveys. (Box 3)
  - Mancoff, Frederick Bennett, Two-dimensional electron transport and magnetoresistance effects in a random magnetic dipole array., June 1995 (Box 3)
  - Mandel, Ilya, Precise trapped flux signal analysis in gravity probe B experiment., June 2000 (Box 3)
  - Manhart, Michael, A model-independent search for new physics at the Large Hadron Collider., June 2009 (Box 3)
  - Mann, E.C., Fabry-Perot imaging of the nearest millisecond pulsar bowshock., June 2001 (Box 3)
  - Mar, Thomas, Dynamics of the moving vortex lattice in two-dimensional disordered superconductors., August 1997 (Box 3)
  - McConnell, Robert, Piezo-induced uniaxial stress in superconducting samples., June 2005 (Box 3)
  - McQuinn, Matthew, The curvature effect and the intrinsic light curves and spectra in GRBs. [2 copies], 2004 (Box 3)
  - Meyer, Jennifer, Dynamical instability and accretion in systems of closely spaced inner moons., May 2006 (Box 3)
  - Monstavicius, Dion, Non-contact charge control using field emission cathodes., June 1998 (Box 3)
  - Morgan, Robert, Snoluminescence and differential light scattering. (Box 3)
  - Murphree, Dennis H., Jr., The design and implementation of a fast programmable trigger for the Kamioka liquid scintillator anti-neutrino detector., June 2000 (Box 3)
  - Nakagawa, Wataru, Low-temperature characterization of avalanche photodiode (APD) in gain mode., June 1996 (Box 3)
  - Niell, Cris, Confocal fluorescence measurement of DNA diffusion., June 1995 (Box 3)
  - Norte, Richard, First-order perturbation solution to the Schrodinger equation for a massive particle's time-dependent sphere of influence., 2007 (Box 4)
  - Nowadnick, Elizabeth, Study of the decay B--> λc + p π-., June 2006 (Box 4)
  - Olding, Benjamin, Computer modeling superconduction magnetic shields., June 1998 (Box 4)
  - Patterson, Brad, An automatic nuclear emulsion scanning system with track recognition., June 2000 (Box 4)
  - Persh, Steven E., Quasar absorption lines as probes for high redshift superclusters., June 1994 (Box 4)
  - Phelps, Steven, The growth of C60 crystals and measurement of their thermal expansion., June 1993 (Box 4)
  - Podolsky, Daniel, Dalitz plot analysis of the decay D+ --> K-π+π+., June 1998 (Box 4)
  - Popovici, Andrei, The scaling of the entanglement spacing in semidilute DNA solutions., June 1995 (Box 4)
  - Risca, Viviana I., "Magneto-optical tweezers": design and construction fo a magnetic tweezers device compatible with an optical trap. [2 copies], June 2004 (Box 4)
  - Rose, Mark and Glenn Wong, Construction of ap hoton scanning tunneling microscope., June 1993 (Box 4)
  - Rosen, Michael J., Charge Kondo effect and enhanced superconductivity in (PbySn1-y)1-xInxTe., June 2006 (Box 4)
  - Rozler, Michael, Use of an STM as a microcontactor to study micron-scale mo/amorphous Si/Mo tunnel junctions., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Ruderman, Joshua, Simulating universal extra dimensions., 2006 (Box 4)
  - Santos, Edward, Optimizing selection criteria for B-->λcl., June 2009 (Box 4)
  - Schlafly, Eddie, Search for high-redshift CGRaBS blazars., June 2007 (Box 4)
  - Sciambi, Adam R., A simple apparatus for the observation of quantized conductance., May 2005 (Box 4)
  - Shapiro, Alexander L., Techniques in low-temperature calorimetry and the heat capacity of silicon carbide (SiC)., April 1993 (Box 4)
  - Simon, Joshua, Probing bulk flows with spiral galaxy rotation curves and the Tully-Fisher relation., June 1998 (Box 4)
  - Solotaroff, Jacob, An investigation of the multiparameter properties and their effect on supernova spectra and distances using multivariate analysis., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Sommer, Ariel, Optimizing the search for Τ- -->λπ- using multivariate analysis., 2007 (Box 4)
  - Stockton, John Kenton, Superconductor-semiconductor hybrid nanostructures. [2 copies], June 1999 (Box 5)
  - Suh, Sunok josephine, Little Higgs models and their classification., June 2009 (Box 5)
  - Tanedo, Philip, Split supersymmetry in the Higgs resonance region., February 2006 (Box 5)
  - Thompson, Matthew C., Development of an atomic interferometry-based gravity gadiometer., June 1997 (Box 5)
  - Tunguz, Bojan, The production of aerogels and the measurement of their surface area using the BET technique., June 1997 (Box 5)
  - Vishik, Inna, Qunatum impurities in the electron-doped high-temperature superconductor neodymium cerium copper oxide: crystal growth, characterization, and magnetic neutron scattering., June 2006 (Box 5)
  - Wai, Lawrence L., The effect of trapped magnetic flux quanta on the London readout in GP-B., June 1989 (Box 5)
  - Wang, Mark M., Examination fo the order parameter symmetry in high temperature superconductors through a study of Josephson coupling., June 1994 (Box 5)
  - White, Olivia L., Studies of exactly-solvable quantum antiferro-magnets., June 1997 (Box 5)
  - Williams, Christopher, Imaging and analyzing EGRET pulsar candidates with the GMRT., June 2005 (Box 5)
  - Williams, Tess, Construction and early stage testing of a Sunyaev Zel'dovich receiver., June 2005 (Box 5)
  - Wohns, Dan, Sequestered inflation., 2006 (Box 5)
  - Yang, Bo, Fabrication and measurement of graphene devices., May 2007 (Box 5)
  - Yeo, Wenzheng, Measurement of T1 electron spin relaxation time in a high-purity n-type GaAs semiconductor., June 2006 (Box 5)
  - Yong, Ee Hou, Relic abundance of the lightest neutralino., June 2003 (Box 5)
  - Zaks, Julia, Investigation of the mobility of regioregular poly-3-hexylthiophene when infiltrated into nanopores., 2007 (Box 5)
  - Zhao, Yue, Measurement of natural widths of Σc++ and Σc0 charmed baryons. [2 copies], May 2004 (Box 5)
  - Zielinski, Lukasz J., Electronic transport in low dimensional GaAs/AlGaAs heterostructures., July 1997 (Box 5)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - DiDonna, Brian, Suspension torque predictions for the relativity gyroscope experiment., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Vandenbroucke, Justin, Acoustic detection of extremely high energy cosmic ray neutrinos: results from an undersea microphone array., 2002 (Box 1)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-180
  - Berger, Seth David, The effect of lower dimensionality on angle-resolved photoemission., 1993 Jun (Box 1)
  - Bernevig, B. A., Hall transition in an anyon gas: non-zero temperature., 2000 Aug 10 (Box 1)
  - Chao, Lambert Key, Low temperature dielectric behavior of silica aerogel., 1998 Jun 14 (Box 1)
  - Cronenwett, Sara Marie, Mesoscopic fluctuations with strong interactions: universal conductance fluctuations of elastic cotunneling., 1996 Jun (Box 1)
  - Cronin, Alex D. and Enadal C. Burns, Experimental observation of electromagnetic emissions due to the fracture of quartz, feldspar, and granodiorite., 1993 Jun 2 (Box 1)
  - Dempsey, Jed, A method for visual pattern recognition in a self-organizing system., 1981 (Box 1)
  - Estrada, Paul R., Voyager observations of the color of Saturn's rings., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Elteto, Klara and Roger W. Romani, Gamma-Ray pulsars as candidates for the unidentified EGRET sources, 2001 June (Box 1)
  - Felson, Wayne Steven, Magnetic dipole and quadrupole readout for ground-based testing of the relativity gyroscope., 1993 Mar (Box 1)
  - Gershow, Marc, An automated wafer inspection system for the cryogenic dark matter search., 2001 Jun 7 (Box 1)
  - Goldman, Mark, Nonlinear dynamics of coupled Josephson Junctions: spatial vs. temporal modes., 1993 Jun 3 (Box 1)
  - Gimon, Eric G., Particle production and radiation from an accelerated mirror., 1993 Jun (Box 1)
  - Hampton, Marshall, The electronic structure and spin-spin coupling of Mn(III)(2)([mu]-oxo)(bis-[mu]-carboxylato) core models of manganese redox enzymes., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Hiatt, Jeremy, Methods of synthesis and characterization of nanostructures bridged by single molecules., 2008 Jun (Box 1)
  - Hohlfeld, Evan B., Quantum phase transitions and black hole vent horizons., 2001 Jan 30 (Box 1)